{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian2.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "venerdi",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1516731933.7514734,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Friday\"?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "martedi",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1516731925.751727,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Tuesday\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lunedi",
                "lenedi"
            ],
            "answer": "Lenedi",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1516731899.387867,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Monday\"?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buona notte",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1516731902.7239475,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"good night\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mercoledi",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1516731931.4557016,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Wednesday\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "arrivederla"
            ],
            "answer": "arrivederLa",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516731920.4640613,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"good-bye (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sessanta",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516731923.1677852,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"60\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e sposata"
            ],
            "answer": "e sposata?",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516731945.8437145,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Are you married?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "febbraio",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1516732133.178331,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"February\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dicassette",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516732078.4584916,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"17\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io ho una famiglia piccola",
                "io ho una famiglia piccola",
                "sono ho una famiglia piccola"
            ],
            "answer": "Io ho una famiglia piccola.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1516732119.4791842,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I have a small family.\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "giovedi"
            ],
            "answer": "Giovedi",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516731995.5786276,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Thursday\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E anche io sono uno studente",
                "e anche io sono uno studente",
                "e anche, io sono uno studente"
            ],
            "answer": "E anche io sono uno studente.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516732130.4186902,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And me, too, I'm a student.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quaranta",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516731977.135812,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"40\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ottobre",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516732108.6058056,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"October\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "diciannove",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516732123.9300406,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"19\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "diciotto",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516732174.8736658,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"18\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "settembre",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516732136.0658822,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"September\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "arrivederci",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516732189.7302144,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"good-bye (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a dopo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732159.0622177,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"see you later\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "settanta",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732177.3387644,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"70\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "luglio",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516732193.2582562,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"July\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "giugno",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732180.7455769,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"June\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prego"
            ],
            "answer": "Prego.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732184.2499921,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You're welcome.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e la figlia",
                "C'e' la figlia",
                "c'e la figlia"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' la figlia.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516732375.2096255,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the daughter.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "io ho un padre",
                "ho un padre"
            ],
            "answer": "Ho un padre.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732210.2216833,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I have a father.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cento",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732270.0057664,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"100\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono il figlio e la figlia",
                "ci sono il figlio e la figlia"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono il figlio e la figlia.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516732367.4328134,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are the son and the daughter.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buona giornata",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516732378.812981,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"have a good day\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gennaio",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732273.3259828,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"January\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "maggio",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516732350.9455948,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"May\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "novanta",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732348.309192,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"90\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "June",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732403.6327221,
            "question": "Given the definition \"giugno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una nipote",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732412.8732593,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a niece\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sette",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732408.3451545,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"7\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a presto",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732415.7132173,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"see you soon\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un ragazzo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732401.028999,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a boy\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "thursday"
            ],
            "answer": "Thursday",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732382.2694578,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Giovedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "agosto",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732405.9538224,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"August\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "piacere mio"
            ],
            "answer": "Piacere mio.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732420.4331653,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Pleased to meet you, too.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lei e una professoressa",
                "lei e' una professoressa"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei e' una professoressa.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732434.6603801,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She's a teacher.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono il fratello e' la sorella",
                "Ci sono il fratello e la sorella"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono il fratello e la sorella.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732474.1935008,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are the brother and sister.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui e un poliziotto",
                "lui e' un poliziotto"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui e' un poliziotto.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732526.6967041,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He's a policeman.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon pomeriggio",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732518.840617,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"good afternoon\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono sposato",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732489.87642,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I am married.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "see you later",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732438.252906,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a dopo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hi"
            ],
            "answer": "hello",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732492.4689145,
            "question": "Given the definition \"salvo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon giorno",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732510.4487407,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"good morning\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sabato",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732528.8723044,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Saturday\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "marzo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732530.944493,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"March\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a family",
                "this is a family"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is a family...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732556.076857,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco una famiglia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e' il figlio",
                "c'e il figlio"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' il figlio.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732545.5887408,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the son.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dicembre",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732581.4562845,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"December\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buona sera",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732559.100432,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"good evening\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "molto bene, grazie"
            ],
            "answer": "Molto bene, grazie.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732537.04484,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Very well, thanks.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "domenica"
            ],
            "answer": "domencia",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732576.03199,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sunday\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quattordici",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732638.984603,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"14\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "have a good evening",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516732633.0398486,
            "question": "Given the definition \"buona serata\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "16",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732608.131628,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sedici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e il fratello",
                "c'e il fratello"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' il fratello.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732592.4602263,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the brother.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come sta?"
            ],
            "answer": "Come sta?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732628.656807,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"How are you doing? (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dieci",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732614.7797346,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"10\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "10",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732594.91649,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dieci\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cinquanta",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732612.6885247,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"50\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quindici",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732660.1314223,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"15\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "niece"
            ],
            "answer": "a niece",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732668.6073465,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una nipote\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Sono di Milano",
                "sono di milano"
            ],
            "answer": "Sono di Milano.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732689.6953287,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I'm from Milan.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cinque",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732652.8994877,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"5\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "grazie mille"
            ],
            "answer": "Grazie mille.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732682.7434072,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Thanks a lot.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cugino",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732685.408366,
            "question": "Given the definition \"male cousin\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "trenta",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732677.5998778,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"30\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "zia",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732655.7234445,
            "question": "Given the definition \"aunt\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "salvo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732694.8716574,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"hello\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dodici",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732716.0196328,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"12\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "venti",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732713.05948,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"20\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buona serata",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732710.7237568,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"have a good evening\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tuesday"
            ],
            "answer": "Tuesday",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732700.1392815,
            "question": "Given the definition \"martedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nonno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732703.7163818,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandfather\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sedici",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732706.6515787,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"16\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E io ho una sorella",
                "e ho una sorella"
            ],
            "answer": "E ho una sorella.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732726.366764,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And I have a sister.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cugina",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732752.4347968,
            "question": "Given the definition \"female cousin\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "july"
            ],
            "answer": "July",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732775.2875812,
            "question": "Given the definition \"luglio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sto bene, grazie",
                "Sto bene, grazie"
            ],
            "answer": "(Sto) Bene, grazie.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732790.7589114,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(I am) Fine, thanks.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cosi-cosi",
                "cosi cosi"
            ],
            "answer": "Cosi, cosi.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732758.6909196,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"So so, not bad.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "friday"
            ],
            "answer": "Friday",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732793.5432029,
            "question": "Given the definition \"venerdi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quattro",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732783.407535,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"4\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "60",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732749.619603,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sessanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Wednesday",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516732786.7269773,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mercoledi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aprile",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732807.3547835,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"April\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a boy",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732797.6556408,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un ragazzo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sei",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732816.0513163,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"6\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She is a teacher",
                "she is a teacher"
            ],
            "answer": "She's a teacher.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732811.8422022,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei e' una professoressa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the sister",
                "this is the sister"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the sister.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732804.354647,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' la sorella.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "90",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732795.4782152,
            "question": "Given the definition \"novanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "9",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732813.6674948,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nove\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lei e;"
            ],
            "answer": "lei e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732820.8272164,
            "question": "Given the definition \"she is\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "may"
            ],
            "answer": "May",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732864.6750512,
            "question": "Given the definition \"maggio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is the father and the mother",
                "these are the father and the mother"
            ],
            "answer": "There are the father and the mother.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732861.666464,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono il padre e la madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "monday"
            ],
            "answer": "Monday",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732837.6071434,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lenedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "15",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732846.7985954,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quindici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "male cousin",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732841.3745568,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cugino\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "17",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732867.5870643,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dicassette\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono il padre e la madre",
                "ci sono il padre e la madre"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono il padre e la madre.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732833.7908773,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are the father and the mother.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un uomo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732852.9222274,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a man\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco una famiglia",
                "ecco una famiglia"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco una famiglia.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732881.1826975,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here is a family...\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "2",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732889.2861784,
            "question": "Given the definition \"due\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e'...",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732900.054661,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is...\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good morning",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732870.7790594,
            "question": "Given the definition \"buon giorno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am married"
            ],
            "answer": "I am married.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732885.326409,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sono sposato\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "novembre",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732887.421986,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"November\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aunt",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732873.2346125,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"zia\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "6",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732901.7180297,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sei\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "12",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732943.8388107,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dodici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una bambina",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732930.6981897,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a child (girl)\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good night",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516732946.446024,
            "question": "Given the definition \"buona notte\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "And I have a mother",
                "and I have a mother"
            ],
            "answer": "And I have a mother.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732936.5189533,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E ho una madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E io ho una madre",
                "E ho una madre",
                "e ho una madre"
            ],
            "answer": "E ho una madre.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732909.882516,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And I have a mother.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e il padre"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' il padre.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732917.5704095,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the father.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Sono di",
                "sono di"
            ],
            "answer": "Sono di...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732922.210488,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am from...\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are",
                "there are"
            ],
            "answer": "There are...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732925.834482,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he is",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732978.946578,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lui e'\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "March",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732960.330104,
            "question": "Given the definition \"marzo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e",
                "ecco e'"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733003.622023,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here is...\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei e' una studentessa",
                "lei e' una studentessa"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei e' una studentessa.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516733017.082108,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She's a student.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "nipote"
            ],
            "answer": "un nipote",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732954.6948023,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a nephew\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "saturday"
            ],
            "answer": "Saturday",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732957.9858017,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sabato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "7",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732976.7461007,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sette\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "THere are the son and the daughter",
                "There are the son and the daughter",
                "There is the son and the daughter"
            ],
            "answer": "There are the son and the daughter.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516732974.5058746,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono il figlio e la figlia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono",
                "ci sono"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733053.7173455,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are...\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "undici",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733023.481744,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"11\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco una donna",
                "ecco una donna"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco una donna.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516733094.8738048,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Her is a woman.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "piacere mio",
                "piacere"
            ],
            "answer": "Piacere.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733030.0772357,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Pleased to meet you.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "And I have a sister",
                "and I have a sister"
            ],
            "answer": "And I have a sister.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733086.461532,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E ho una sorella.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lui e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733019.6584094,
            "question": "Given the definition \"he is\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Pleased to meet you",
                "pleased to meet you"
            ],
            "answer": "Pleased to meet you.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733079.0843236,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Piacere.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tredici",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733090.7816477,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"13\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io sono Francessco",
                "Io sono Francesco"
            ],
            "answer": "Io sono Francesco.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733111.1453109,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I'm Francessco.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you're welcome"
            ],
            "answer": "You're welcome.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733123.7253168,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Prego.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the mother",
                "there is the mother",
                "there's the mother"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the mother.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733103.0419326,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' la madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "14",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733120.8208866,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quattordici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nove",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733118.3604586,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"9\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "4",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733113.0022326,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quattro\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "and you?",
                "and you (formal)"
            ],
            "answer": "...and you? (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733116.6096766,
            "question": "Given the definition \"...e Lei?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e la sorella",
                "c'e' la sorella"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' la sorella.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733134.8056374,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the sister.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Sunday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733166.737493,
            "question": "Given the definition \"domencia\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are the brother and the sister",
                "there are the brother and sister"
            ],
            "answer": "There are the brother and sister.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733162.193658,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono il fratello e la sorella.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come stai?"
            ],
            "answer": "Come stai?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733169.736928,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"How are you doing? (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "18",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733137.4936807,
            "question": "Given the definition \"diciotto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e lei?"
            ],
            "answer": "...e Lei?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733172.6891296,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"...and you? (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un bambino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733177.8533049,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a child (boy)\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "thanks"
            ],
            "answer": "Thank you.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733174.7090907,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Grazie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "1",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733163.8007467,
            "question": "Given the definition \"uno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "100",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733179.9653265,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cento\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here",
                "here / there"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733183.0849836,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am Francesco"
            ],
            "answer": "I'm Francessco.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733187.5492275,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io sono Francesco.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e tu?"
            ],
            "answer": "...et tu?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733190.620481,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"...and you? (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a baby girl"
            ],
            "answer": "a child (girl)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733209.11356,
            "question": "Given the definition \"una bambina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a woman",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733196.1404922,
            "question": "Given the definition \"una donna\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "My name is"
            ],
            "answer": "My name is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733193.693268,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Mi chiamo...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "80",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733206.337153,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ottanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good evening",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733226.6486032,
            "question": "Given the definition \"buona sera\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I have a small family"
            ],
            "answer": "I have a small family.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733235.9888167,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io ho una famiglia piccola.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "5",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733223.3688357,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cinque\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She is a student",
                "she is a student"
            ],
            "answer": "She's a student.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733221.6888661,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei e' una studentessa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Thanks a lot"
            ],
            "answer": "Thanks a lot.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733211.8089225,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Grazie mille.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "and you (informal)",
                "and you?"
            ],
            "answer": "...and you? (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733216.5213299,
            "question": "Given the definition \"...et tu?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e la madre"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' la madre.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733232.1169395,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the mother.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "He is a policeman"
            ],
            "answer": "He's a policeman.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733241.1407564,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui e' un poliziotto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "8",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733248.0520906,
            "question": "Given the definition \"otto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Mi chiamo",
                "mi chiamo"
            ],
            "answer": "Mi chiamo...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733246.5649018,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My name is...\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grandmother",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733260.800034,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nonna\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the daughter"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the daughter.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733265.1523118,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' la figlia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nonna",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733251.5840645,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandmother\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am Italian"
            ],
            "answer": "I'm Italian.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733257.936314,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sono italiano.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "30",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733267.2481995,
            "question": "Given the definition \"trenta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "50",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733269.3923016,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cinquanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good afternoon",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733298.7883933,
            "question": "Given the definition \"buon pomeriggio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733275.8405552,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"3\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "40",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733274.3520048,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quaranta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733271.3846478,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"2\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "And also I am a student",
                "also I am a student"
            ],
            "answer": "And me, too, I'm a student.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733284.8047156,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E anche io sono uno studente.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uncle",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733295.4525328,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"zio\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "goodbye (informal)",
                "goodby (informal)"
            ],
            "answer": "good-bye (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733291.7567167,
            "question": "Given the definition \"arrivederci\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "grazie"
            ],
            "answer": "Grazie.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733301.5648394,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Thank you.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hello, goodbye"
            ],
            "answer": "hi, hello, goodbye",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733305.5517938,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ciao\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "how are you (informal)"
            ],
            "answer": "How are you doing? (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733314.865117,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Come stai?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "female cousin",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733310.39965,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cugina\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a person",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733318.6576157,
            "question": "Given the definition \"una persona\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "goodbye (formal)"
            ],
            "answer": "good-bye (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733323.16811,
            "question": "Given the definition \"arrivederLa\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am from",
                "I'm from"
            ],
            "answer": "I am from...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516733340.5088832,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sono di...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "otto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733316.608499,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"8\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pleased to meet you",
                "Pleased to meet you"
            ],
            "answer": "Pleased to meet you, too.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733335.916589,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Piacere mio.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "How are you (formal)",
                "how are you? (formal)"
            ],
            "answer": "How are you doing? (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733361.2957351,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Come sta?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "19",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733345.1640065,
            "question": "Given the definition \"diciannove\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "zio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733349.4120522,
            "question": "Given the definition \"uncle\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the brother",
                "there is the brother"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the brother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733354.5876932,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' il fratello.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733347.0604153,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"1\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "January",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733364.5444038,
            "question": "Given the definition \"gennaio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ciao",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733342.598328,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"hi, hello, goodbye\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She is"
            ],
            "answer": "she is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733370.6966474,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lei e'\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the father"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the father.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733383.8840346,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' il padre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a girl",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733390.6357555,
            "question": "Given the definition \"una ragazza\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "13",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733373.1758573,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tredici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a baby boy"
            ],
            "answer": "a child (boy)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733380.2238927,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un bambino\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "December",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733386.3323042,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dicembre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "20",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733374.8164525,
            "question": "Given the definition \"venti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Sono Italiano"
            ],
            "answer": "Sono italiano.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733394.499186,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I'm Italian.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ottanta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733396.8360822,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"80\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "11",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733413.5997303,
            "question": "Given the definition \"undici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "see you soon",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733401.203202,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a presto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "3",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733398.3077528,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "April",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733411.775666,
            "question": "Given the definition \"aprile\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I have a father"
            ],
            "answer": "I have a father.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733409.608257,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ho un padre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a man",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733403.3558583,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un uomo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "una bambina / ragazza"
            ],
            "answer": "una ragazza",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733420.2475479,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a girl\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "so-so"
            ],
            "answer": "So so, not bad.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733405.6197934,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Cosi, cosi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "November",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733442.4843268,
            "question": "Given the definition \"novembre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "September",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733458.32354,
            "question": "Given the definition \"settembre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am from Milan",
                "I'm from Milan"
            ],
            "answer": "I'm from Milan.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733425.336541,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sono di Milano.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Have a good day"
            ],
            "answer": "have a good day",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733450.8277404,
            "question": "Given the definition \"buona giornata\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Very good, thanks",
                "I'm good, thanks"
            ],
            "answer": "Very well, thanks.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733431.775344,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Molto bene, grazie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is a woman",
                "here is a woman"
            ],
            "answer": "Her is a woman.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733455.7951143,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco una donna.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una persona",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733439.8117387,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a person\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is",
                "there is"
            ],
            "answer": "There is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733435.8637266,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Are you married?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733469.1836367,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"e sposata?\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Grandfather"
            ],
            "answer": "grandfather",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733463.9516306,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nonno\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "august"
            ],
            "answer": "August",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733475.4710293,
            "question": "Given the definition \"agosto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "nephew"
            ],
            "answer": "a nephew",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733492.0511441,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un nipote\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "October",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733478.903857,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ottobre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the son",
                "there is the son"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the son.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733497.6113253,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' il figlio.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una donna",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733485.7120936,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a woman\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "70",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733471.8472269,
            "question": "Given the definition \"settanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'm good, thanks",
                "I'm good, thank you"
            ],
            "answer": "(I am) Fine, thanks.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733501.6677678,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(Sto) Bene, grazie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "February",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516733504.6202135,
            "question": "Given the definition \"febbraio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        }
    ]
}